<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<destinations>
  <destination>
    <name>Kabugsakan Falls</name>
    <location>
      <address>Barangay Tugos, Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/falls2.jpg</image>
    <description>Must-visit destination for nature lovers, history enthusiasts, and those seeking a tranquil getaway. Ideal for picnics and nature-based activities, it is a popular spot among the locals being proximate to the poblacion of Boac.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Hinulugang Amerikano</name>
    <location>
      <address>Brgy. PutinG Buhangin, Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/falls.jpg</image>
    <description>Waterfall also serves as a reminder of Marinduque's history and cultural heritage. A popular tourist attraction located in Boac, Marinduque, in the Philippines. It is a scenic waterfall that holds historical significance due to its connection.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Banhigan Falls</name>
    <location>
      <address>Brgy. Duyay, Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/falls3.jpg</image>
    <description>Tucked away in the lush and verdant landscape, the falls offer a serene and enchanting retreat for visitors. To reach Banhigan Falls, you may embark on a scenic trek through the tropical forests, crossing rivers, and traversing rocky terrains.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Sea of Clouds</name>
    <location>
      <address>Sitio Baliis, Brgy Bantay Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/nature.jpg</image>
    <description>They are there to experience the Sea of Clouds and the remarkable scenery offered as they gaze upon the forest hills and mountains below where barangays of the once forlorn Mahinhin and Hinapulan are nestled.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Roberto Beach Resort</name>
    <location>
      <address>Sitio Baliis, Brgy Bantay Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/beach.jpg</image>
    <description>This is where life blends with nature and nature blends with you. Three decades later, nothing close to the dream was realized albeit construction and improvements to existing interior roads in Boac were becoming more visible!</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>A&A Resort</name>
    <location>
      <address>Barangay Laylay, Boac Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/beach2.jpg</image>
    <description>Newly opened quiet and private hotel and beach resort located in Marinduque, an island province in the heart of the Philippines. Open for events and staycations of your family. Hassle-free trip while enjoying the services and amenities.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Buliasnin Beach</name>
    <location>
      <address>Barangay Buliasnin Boac Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/beach3.jpg</image>
    <description>This is where life blends with nature and nature blends with you. Three decades later, nothing close to the dream was realized albeit construction and improvements to existing interior roads in Boac were becoming more visible!</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Eco Park Resort</name>
    <location>
      <address>Baranagay Bunaganay Boac Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/resort.jpg</image>
    <description>A great choice for a stay in Boac, Freedom Eco Adventure Park by Cocotel powered by fave features a free water park. Powered by fave also features barbecue grills, a garden, and concierge services. Self-parking is free.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Dayo</name>
    <location>
      <address>Baranagay Balogo Boac Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/food.jpg</image>
    <description>There is a new popular eatery with a variety of delicious food and drinks. Many come here to celebrate their birthdays and achievements in life. Many tourists also come here. Their service here will see the hospitality of Marinduquenos.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Goodchow</name>
    <location>
      <address>Brgy, Bayan ng Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/food2.jpg</image>
    <description>The roadside café at the ground floor serves burgers, pizzas, chicken, French fries, pasta, noodles, sandwiches, sipao, halo-halo, and siomai. An air-conditioned dining room extension that serves lunch and dinner.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>10.y.o cafe</name>
    <location>
      <address>Brgy. Balaring, Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/food3.jpg</image>
    <description>10.y.o cafe one of the best restaurants in Boac Marinduque. This is one of the restaurants that tourists flock to in Boac Marinduque. The quality of service and speed of service is deteriorating over time. And the quality of food could be more consistent.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Kusina sa Plaza</name>
    <location>
      <address>Brgy, Bayan ng Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/food4.jpg</image>
    <description>Is a go-to destination for those looking to savor authentic Filipino and Marinduqueño cuisine while enjoying the lively atmosphere of the town's plaza. It is a place where locals and visitors can gather to indulge in delectable dishes and create memorable dining experiences.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Marina Hotel</name>
    <location>
      <address>Brgy. Balaring, Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/hotel.jpg</image>
    <description>Serves local and international cuisine. Recreational activities at the resort such as swimming, snorkeling, and diving. They also have a fitness center, a spa, and a game room. Perfect destination for travelers who are looking for a relaxing and enjoyable beachfront experience.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Nine Balconies Island Stay</name>
    <location>
      <address>Nepomuceno St., Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/hotel2.jpg</image>
    <description>Offers unique recreational opportunities for all guests. Be sure to spend some time exploring the beach, which is accessible directly from the inn. End your days in total relaxation with a visit to the salon, located right at the inn. Sip your favorite cocktail outdoors at the inn's poolside bar.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Hotel Zenturia</name>
    <location>
      <address>Isok 1, Boac Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/hotel4.jpg</image>
    <description>The best choice for visitors who are searching for comfort, cleanliness, and backed by a friendly and accommodating staff who are available to attend to customer's needs. Splendid service together with a wide range of facilities provided will make you complain for nothing during your stay.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Balar Hotel</name>
    <location>
      <address>Brgy. Balaring, Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/hotel3.jpg</image>
    <description>Balar Hotel and Spa has a full-service spa that offers a range of treatments and massages, as well as a fitness center for guests who want to keep active during their stay. The hotel also has a restaurant, the Balar Café.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Boac Cathedral</name>
    <location>
      <address>Brgy. Mataas na Bayan Boac Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/church.jpg</image>
    <description>The Immaculate Conception Cathedral Parish, commonly referred to as Boac Cathedral, is a Roman Catholic church and cathedral in the town center of Boac, Marinduque, in the Mimaropa region of the Philippines.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>National Museum</name>
    <location>
      <address>Brgy. Balaring, Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/museum.jpg</image>
    <description>Features the rich heritage. It was also utilized as the Boac Municipal Library. Beside the Boac Town Plaza and Rizal Park, is home to a collection of facts and information about the Island.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Boac Town Arena</name>
    <location>
      <address>Brgy. San Miguel Boac, Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/museum.jpg</image>
    <description>The Boac Town Arena is where the famous senakulo, a part of the celebration of Moriones Festival, is held.</description>
  </destination>
  <destination>
    <name>Laylay Port</name>
    <location>
      <address>Barangay Laylay Boac Marinduque</address>
    </location>
    <image>images/port.jpg</image>
    <description>This a historical landmark in the municipality where the Japanese and American troops landed.</description>
  </destination>
</destinations>
